Oh
Has to keep your love coming.
Thank you.
Eternal farewell, Niko Robin, the woman who draws darkness.
We're here! We're here! Come on, Granny! Hurry! Hurry!
Calm down. Get a hold of yourself.
What a seven. It's been a while.
Granny! Hurry! Hurry!
Okay, okay!
Attention all passengers! Wearing a mask on the sea train today is strictly prohibited.
Look, ma'am, just cooperate and show me your face.
This is my face. See?
Huh? Hey, you.
Oh, uh, Miss Kokoro. So nice to see you again.
What's going on here? Trouble?
Yes, yes, ma'am. Everyone is on the lookout for the Straw Hat Pirates, the culprits in the attempted assassination of Iceberg.
Icebergs? Assassins?
What is it, Granny? Huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
Huh?
I'm falling! I'm falling! I'm falling! I'm falling!
I'm falling! I'm falling!
Whoa!
Whew! Good. Safe and sound.
Yeah. That wore me out, huh?
Safe and sound my butt! I thought I was gonna die!
What was I supposed to do? You were the one who said we couldn't use the elevator because we get caught! I didn't have a choice!
That doesn't mean, hey, let's jump down, idiot! You can't glide around like that square-nosed shipwright! Got it?
Right. Sorry about that.
Whatever. It's fine since we're safe now.
Then stop hitting me!
However, we might not be safe for long.
We won't? Why not? What's wrong?
This island's topography and climate. With this much wind blowing and the atmospheric pressure falling so rapidly, there's likely going to be a typhoon here tonight.
This place is called the City of Water. Think about it. Its greatest weakness would have to be flooding.
Okay, so it floods, so what?
Well, it worries me, that's all. I'll check into it later.
Come on, let's head back to the inn for the time being.
Hey there. Welcome. How are ya?
Ow! How's everything going, Bluno?
Feelin' super!
Yeah, well, I suppose you could say that.
What do you mean, suppose? You're not a very decisive guy, are you? I'll take the usual. Fill her up, please!
Do you got any money? Just fill them up, will ya? Cola!
I think you run an establishment like this with the greedy notion of taking money from your customers.
We do have a little money.
About a million berries left from our shopping spree.
What? We have that much left? How disgraceful! How totally uncool to think that I didn't spend it all in one night!
Here, give me that!
Wow! Listen up! This is your lucky day, customers!
All your drinks are on me! Knock back as much booze as you like!
Compliments of me, your pal Frankie!
Yay! That's our Frankie! You're the best!
The face of one or seventh underworld! What a guy!
Whoa! That's awesome! Look over here! It's pal-dum-
So, Bluno, where's my cola? Come on, hurry it up already!
Looks like business has been good for you, Frankie.
Ugh!
Old Hat Kokoro! That was you I sat next to?
I thought it was a statue of a sea monster!
Granny! Is it okay for me to get a refill of my juice then?
Hey kid, this is a bar. It's no place for little shrimps like you!
Business has been good, right?
Ugh! Fine, whatever! Suit yourself!
Hooray! Juice!
Yeah, business has been outstanding, but I feel terrible!
In fact, this entire week has been a total downer!
And it's all because of that stupid pirate!
Here you go, full take!
Good! Took you long enough!
Fuel! Fuel! Fuel! Fuel! Fuel!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Super!
There! Completely restored!
That bastard, wait till I get my hands on him!
Hey, Hag! Why are you here?
Aqua Laguna is on its way.
Is that right? No wonder the wind's blowing so strong today.
You need to get your house prepped up for the storm.
Well, there's nothing much to prep really, seeing as how I don't actually have a house anymore.
I was going to have a drink with Iceberg, but it seems he was shot.
Yeah, I heard about that. They say pirates are responsible.
Gallylaw and the townspeople are raging pissed.
So a pirate did it, huh?
Do you honestly think that's what happened?
Hey, you sound like you know something. If you really do, then spit it out, you old hag!
Iceberg's constantly being hounded by the world government. You ever notice that?
So? Wait, are you trying to say that government lapdog Corgi pulled the trigger?
That little troll isn't cut out to try something like that.
You're right. That assassination plot falls more in line with the work of CP9.
Is that right, Bluto? Ever heard of him?
Only rumors, really.
Jeez, you village simpletons sure put a lot of stock into stories about imaginary boogeyman shadow organizations.
Don't be an idiot. Of course they exist. They just never show themselves.
Can't really work undercover if everyone knows who you are.
You seem pretty sure of yourself. Got some kind of proof about this?
Nope, just rumors.
Stop screwing around, hag! Look, rumors are superstitious nonsense!
Strange they've remained a rumor for such a long time, huh?
They're good at eliminating people without anyone noticing.
If you mess with them, you're dead meat.
Impressive work. The assignment we had to do yesterday would very well.
Excellent job, Nico Robin.
Thanks, it was a cakewalk.
Though naturally, you're now being pursued by every last person in the city.
Indeed I am.
Merely a temporary setback.
Tonight is what's important. Understand?
We'll infiltrate Iceberg's residents one more time.
If it becomes a worst case scenario, you're free to eliminate all of the evidence.
Among Tom's apprentices who could have had it from the very beginning,
Iceberg is the only one that remains alive.
No matter how much he denies having it in the name of CP9,
we will take it tonight.
Never forget, this is a mission of justice.
In compliance with the Aqua Laguna warning that was issued for the entire island earlier today,
all docks on the shipbuilding island are now to be considered public shelter and evacuation centers.
Large crowds are expected, so please take shelter as quickly as possible.
Additionally, keep in mind that Dock 1 is currently in a dangerous state.
Alright, I'll put the iron board on.
Hey, honey, you sure we have everything we'll need?
Yes, now come on. We need to take shelter in the shipyard.
Yeah, Dad, let's get going!
Come on, hurry!
Patience, patience. You gotta be careful sealing this board.
If the inside of our house gets flooded, everything will be ruined.
Tie that side down too! Move it!
Hey! The wind is starting to pick up!
The waves will be here anytime now! Hurry!
If we take too long, those assassin pirates are gonna show up too!
What?
Where'd he disappear to? I'm sure he went this way!
He's gotta be around here!
Okay, you guys look over there!
Right!
What the hell is going on? Are they chasing me? I don't understand.
Wait a sec. Is this why everyone's chasing after me?
Culprits in the assassination plot.
Well, that sucks. Can't go back to the inn now. I'll be out in the open.
Hey! Who goes there? Who are you?
Over here! There's a suspicious guy hiding in the alley!
You sure about this? There's no mistake?
I'm certain. They've been staying here at the inn since they checked in last night.
They took off just a little while ago.
They're staying here?
Yes, that's right. They still have lots of luggage left in their room.
I'm sure they'll be back for it sometime.
Right. You guys stay here, okay?
The rest of you, search the surrounding area with me.
Look sharp. Leave no stone unturned. Does everybody got it?
Yeah!
No one's here. Are you 100% certain that this is their ship?
There's no mistaking it! Look up there! That's the flag of the Straw Hat Pirates!
They probably already abandoned her. She's all worn out.
Did you find them? No, they're gone.
There's not much left on board. Pretty sure she was abandoned and left to sink.
Let's keep looking around.
Who were those guys?
Is there something going on in the city?
Find anything? Not a trace of them. Damn it! Where are they?
They sure are persistent.
Hey, Luffy?
Huh? What is it, Nami?
Do you think everybody's okay? These guys are all over the place!
Chopper and Sanji are probably safe because no one knows their faces yet, but still...
Come on, we need to hurry!
Right!
It looks like the C-Train's still in operation.
I guess the noon departure has already left.
There's another one scheduled for tonight, even in all this bad weather.
The 11 PM, leaving for Annie's lobby.
That C-Train is pretty impressive.
Hey! Any news on those pirates?
We've got nothing.
If we can capture just one of those three from the wanted posters, we'll make them cough up who the others are.
Hurry! Before the waves get too high!
Maybe we can't find Robin because she got on the C-Train.
Well, if she did, that would make things worse than they already are. Water 7's too big an area to cover on its own.
What if... what if I did something to upset her back at the bookstore?
Don't be ridiculous. No way that's the reason.
Hey, excuse me. Have you seen a beautiful woman who kinda looks like this?
You mean the one who's about 20 years older than that picture?
If I had, I would have told the newspapers or the galley law company about it.
To think she's an assassin. Kinda shocking, huh?
I admire you for trying to track down that criminal, but I suggest you find yourself some shelter soon.
Aqua Laguna is on its way.
Take care.
Things are getting dangerous around here.
What about the others? Think they're okay?
I'm sure Luffy's fine. Nami's the one that I'm really worried about right now.
At any rate, this city's becoming quite the ghost town.
The wind's really picking up. I'm sure most people are already in the shelter.
Where could she be?
Hey, Robin! Where are you?
That scent... is it...
Chopper? What is it? Chopper?
Chopper?
Hey! Wait for me!
I'm close.
Chopper! Wait up! What's going on, dammit?
This way.
Hey! Chopper! Chopper!
Chopper!
Are you alright?
Foope...
This one is going to work?
To commerce...
Cl excessive heavy heat...
In effect?
scariest...
This one needs a bigger heat...
To complex heat...
A fake lacks less.
He is an Rivera!
These two designs got the same bite of!
Oh, she's not afraid of that.
疲れ果てた向きの中でも変わらないもの探すコンバスで いつまでも持っていれるから
いつかたどり着く夢の終わりに できるだけこのままで大人に
見上げた果てしないこの大空に 永遠に 永遠に
幼き頃の夢物語 忘られち記憶の糸辿り 未だ胸を焦がす残り火を消してしまわないように
乱れた羽渡るこの空に 仲間と共に想いを託し 移り変わる時代を越え 永遠に永遠に
僕たちは目未だと言われます 一通り 誰に聞かないんだ
やに追いこう僕たちうのは vontピース?
greeted部 誕 Add suspense komentで龍のストRAWHATS
Kesればいい fortress
?
.